&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：不久前我在想为什么人们
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: A while back I was thinking about this question of why people
说得好，你为什么不能让它们自动绑定呢？
say well, why couldn't you just make them autobound?
这样我就不必每次都做这个作业了？
And make it so that I don't have to do this assignment every time?
JavaScript不能自动为我做这件事吗？
Couldn't JavaScript just do this automatically for me?
事实上，我认为有一个建议。
In fact I think there is a proposal.
我不知道它是否会发生，但我认为有一个提议
I don't know if it's ever gonna happen, but I think there is a proposal for
一个名为@Bound的类装饰符，
a class decorator called @bound,
这将使您的所有类方法自动绑定。
which would make all your class methods auto-bound.
所以这至少是他们考虑在某个时候做的事情，
So this is at least something that they're considering doing at some point,
是为了让你可以选择加入这个自动绑定。
is making it so that you can opt into this auto-bound.
你也许可以从我的语气中看出，
And you probably can tell from my tone,
在这一点上，我认为这不是一个好主意。
at this point, that I don't think that's a great idea.
但我想通过一个代码思维实验来说明为什么这是一个坏主意。
But I wanna illustrate why it's such a bad idea through a code thought experiment.
我坐下来，我想，我们怎么才能做到这一点呢？
I sat down and I thought, how would we make it so
我们可以在原型上有方法，但是
that we could have methods on a prototype, but
不知何故也有响应实例的自动硬绑定方法？
somehow also have auto hardbound methods that respond to the instances?
我得出的结论是，这是一个黑客。
And I came to the conclusion, there's a hack for this.
看起来是这样的。
And here's what it looks like.
我们要做的是，我不指望你读这个代码。
What we will do is, and I'm not expecting you to read this code.
如果你真的感兴趣，我可以放大，但是
I could zoom in if you were really interested, but
我不指望你读这个代码。
I'm not expecting you to read this code.
只是这个特定的实用程序方法接受现有的
It's just that this particular utility method takes an existing
方法，并将其替换为getter。
method on one of your prototype objects, and replaces it with a getter.
所以换句话说，不是让你的真正方法在你的类原型上，
So in other words, instead of having your real method on your class prototype,
你会有一个吸气剂。
you're gonna have a getter.
因此当您通过getter访问属性名称时，
So when you access that property name through the getter,
它自动为以下对象创建硬绑定方法
it automatically creates a hard bound method for
然后将其保存到WeakMap中。
you on the fly, and then saves it into a WeakMap.
因此它将其缓存到WeakMap中并
So it caches it into a WeakMap and
然后通过getter的方式发送给您。
then sends it out to you through by way of a getter.
换句话说，getter就像一个代理，自动销售这些硬件
In other words, the getter is acting like a proxy to automatically vend these hard
绑定或这些自动硬绑定函数为您。
bound or these auto hard bound functions for you.
因此，您可以在原型上获得一个函数，该函数可以
And so you get the benefit of having a function on the prototype that can
被继承。
be inherited.
但是每次你把它作为上下文点访问时，
But every time you access it as a context dot,
你会得到它的硬装订版本。
you're gonna get a hard bound version of it.
这就是为什么这是一个如此糟糕的想法的例证。
This is an illustration of why this is such a terrible idea.
为了得到一些有用的东西而不得不去做那种丑陋的工作，
To have to go to that kinda level of ugly hackery to get something to work,
它只是不符合JavaScript函数的DNA。
it just doesn't fit with the DNA of JavaScript's functions.
这个感知函数的全部目的是使它们可以是动态的。
The whole purpose of this aware functions is so that they can be dynamic.
并试图迫使他们进入另一种工作模式，
And trying to force them into this other mode of working,
就像其他语言的类一样，
which is like classes in other languages,
就是为什么我们会落得这样糟糕的下场。
is why we wind up with terrible hacky crap like that.
但是，人们喜欢这样做
But, people like to do that and
这可能最终会直接在JavaScript中本机登陆。
this might actually end up landing natively, directly in JavaScript.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：顺便说一下，你是如何使用这个疯狂的小工具的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Here's how you use that by the way, this crazy little utility.
只需调用绑定方法即可使用它
You can use it by simply calling that bind methods
任何类的原型上的实用工具。
utility on the prototype of any class.
它会自动遍历所有的类原型方法，
And it'll automatically go through all of your class prototype methods,
并用执行自动绑定方法的getter版本替换它们。
and replace them with getter versions that do the auto-bind method.
令我恐惧的是，前几天我在推特上发了这个来打招呼，
And to my horror, I tweeted this out the other day to say hey,
这是一个非常糟糕的主意，原因如下。
this is a really bad idea and here's why.
然后我收到了一些人的回复说
And then I got several responses from people saying
我现在我的项目中使用这个。
I'm now using this in my projects.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：[笑]&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So,
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：著名的名言之一，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: One of the famous quotes,
我甚至不知道该归功于谁，但我喜欢的名言是
I don't even know who to attribute it to, but famous quotes that I love is there's
没有什么比临时黑客更永久的了。
nothing more permanent than a temporary hacker.